Abdelrahman Mohamed

Cairo | 01110828568 abdelrahman.mohamed8568@gmail.com

Summary

Here I'm front-end developer with a passion for learning and creating. I have a proven ability to quickly learn new skills and apply them in building responsive and user-friendly web applications. I have experience in Next.js and React. I love applying responsive design principles and seeing my web pages adapt to mobile screens while still looking Amazing. Although I Currently work as a freelance programmer alongside my primary job, I'm Always developing my skills and researching new technology to learn and adapt.

Skills

Next.js, TypeScript, Framer Motion, Netlify, Redux, React Router, React Bootstrap, REST API, React, Swiper.js, GitHub, Git, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML 5, UI/UX, Photoshop

Experience

Freelancers

Front End Web Developer | 02/2023 - Present

- -Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- -Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.
- -Translated UX and business requirements into elegant code solutions.
- -Identified and resolved website performance flags to improve functionality.

Market Makers

Technical Support Specialist | 10/2022 - Present

- -I provide technical support to the company and troubleshoot systems.
- -I prioritize my workload to make sure the most important issues are solved first.
- -Communicate with my co-workers to effectively diagnose problems.

Attijariwafa Bank Egypt -

Sales Staff | 07/2022 - 12/2022

- -Trained and mentored new sales representatives.
- -Created professional sales presentations and seminars to effectively demonstrate product features and competitive advantages.
- -Retained excellent client satisfaction ratings through outstanding service delivery.

B TECH

Customer Service Call Center Agent | 01/2018 - 05/2018

- -Achieved high satisfaction rating through proactive one-call resolutions of customer issues.
- -Learned and maintained in-depth understanding of product and service information to offer knowledgeable and educated responses to diverse customer questions.

Education

Ain Shams University Bachelor Of Law | 06/2020

Certificates

Advanced React (META), React Basics (META), Programming with JavaScript (META), Version Control (META), HTML and CSS in depth (META), Introduction to Front-End Development (META), Web Development Challenger (UDACITY), KICKOFF BANKING

ACADEMY FROM (BUE)

Profiles

-Website: abdelrahmanmohamed.netlify.app

-LinkedIn: abdelrahman-mohamed8568

-GitHub: abdelrahman-mohamed8568

Languages

English, Arabic

Info

-Date of Birth: (29/5/1998)

-Military Status: (Completed)